What would you do when you find out that your boss
is not only smarter than you but also work much harder than you?
What would you do? I will take a pause and let you think about it.
The thing I like the most is your frankness, openness on everything you say
The thing I felt strongest is the determination on everything you do
Evangelos, last year you really let me know
what is the difference between the Virgo and Capricorn.
I am very impressed by your working style,
the preciseness, always try to make things perfect.
I am a little Virgo, following with you.
Evangelos is a very nice man,
and he is a humorous speaker
that every time I learned a lot from his speech.
Evangelos, thanks for initiating the leadership training for us.
It is really inspiring and I get a lot out of it.
Thanks for sharing with us the external events and your insight,
looking forward to hearing more.
Thank you very much to set up a very high bar
and show us example, especially what is a real true leader should be.
He is also very supportive to Shanghai female network group.
I can feel how much he valued diversity and inclusion.
Hey Evangelos, I do some research on your name.
There are two famous Evangelos in Greek Mythology.
One was a shepherd who helped build the Temple of Artemis
and was worshiped because he brought the good news.
The second was a prophet and he was worshiped because
he was the one who announced the good oracles.
So, Evangelos, bring us the good news and good future,
and we will worship you the same.
Thank you very much. I am looking forward to working with you in 2018.
We look forward to working with you in 2018.
Are we comfortable yet? Not yet. However, we are on the way.
Looking forward to working with you in 2018.
Looking forward to another rewarding and challenge year.